辛普森一家
第二十五季 第三集
SPS 辛普森一家字幕组倾情呈现
字幕仅供学习交流之用 本片版权归FOX所有
再过一小时牛奶过期 感谢日光节约时
(也称夏令时 为节省用电量所采用的时间制)
我们会非常想念你的 K老师
翻译: 偏执绝非过错 井脑湿 大曦瓜
校对: 我就是姓刘  后期: 旗木 盖罗
春田镇
谢尔比维尔 巧克力王国 家畜王国 古怪镇
莱克斯自助停车场 James L. Brook(辛普森一家制片人)
舒适的沙发
沙发时刻:
六部曲之一
好寂寞
So lonely.
没戒指就甭想荤
No sex without a ring.
该死
Damn it!
精灵驿站
没小矮子也无爱尔兰人
搞什么... ?!
What the... ?!
还有我们呢 哥们?
What about us, man?
自己整沙发去
Get your own couch.
春田第一教堂 Chip Davis葬礼
你素未谋面的春田至爱人物
受人爱戴的丈夫 父亲 镇民大会常客
1992-1996年以及2008年间饰演Duff侠
春田大牌子文字校订 杂耍Chip 圆顶碎屑清理总监
可怜的Chip 在大家生命里都划下了痕迹
Poor Chip. Such a big part of everyone's life.
人们说他是第六个辛普森家的人
People called him the "sixth Simpson."
我不知道为啥
I'm not sure why.
Chip曾经给我写了一本出奇精彩的传记
Chip did such a wonderful job with my biography.
伟大的混球
Hans Moleman的一生及其所爱
Chip开导我度过了父母因玩彩弹射击不幸过世的灰色时期
Chip是核电站6-F区的灵魂人物
Chip was the life of Sector 6-F at the nuclear plant,
但Chip也曾向我坦白 他确实还有一些遗憾
but Chip once confessed to me he did have a few regrets.
Chip遗憾自己从没从南坡征服过春田峰
Chip regretted never ascending Mount Springfield from the south face.
遗憾自己的高中跳高记录受助于风力帮助
He regretted that the high school long jump record he set was wind-aided.
这事他不止一次提过
He often spoke of that asterisk.
他遗憾从没降服春田迷你高尔夫场第17球洞
He never broke par on hole 17 at Springfield Mini Golf.
让我们祈祷
Let us pray.
人非圣贤 孰无遗憾
Eh, everyone has regrets.
- 我没哦 - 你?
- Not me. - You?
你的婚姻就是浮在一滩走气啤酒上的死鱼
Your marriage is a dead fish floating in a tank of stale beer.
你家幺妹是个吸奶嘴儿狂
Your baby's addicted to pacifiers.
你儿子更是无法无天
And your son is out of control.
请起立行跪
Let us kneel.
我的膝盖
My knees!
Namath: 前美国橄榄球四分卫
四十年休养 全白费了
40 years of healing, gone!
他还真是个淘气鬼
He's such a little dickens.
不过人家狄更斯其实很有教养的
Although Dickens was pretty well behaved.
英国作家 此处为同音异意
他注定完蛋
He's been screwed up...
早在Homer的DNA游向你子宫的时候就是了
since the moment Homer's DNA staggered into your womb.
我才不会为那个遗憾
I have no regrets about that.
那是一段完美的妊娠期
It was a perfect pregnancy.
不抽烟 不喝酒 还掉了三磅肉
Didn't smoke, didn't drink, lost three pounds.
而且每晚睡前 Homer都会为我放送KISS...
And every night before bed, Homer would give me a little kiss...
音乐
music!
KISS: 美国摇滚发展历程中的重要乐队
难道Bart是被怀胎时候的KISS音乐给带坏的?
Could Bart have been prenatally screwed up by the KISS music?
KISS破坏者
♪ 站起来 大家全都动起双脚 ♪
♪ Get up! Everybody's gonna move their feet ♪
♪ 都坐下 迟早你要离开座位 ♪
♪ Get down! Everybody's gonna leave their seats ♪
♪ 你必将丧失理智 就在底特律摇滚城 ♪
♪ You got to lose your mind in Detroit Rock City. ♪
天啊 这真是史上最狂野的孕妈呐喊了
Man, this is the weirdest pregnancy craving ever.
不管怎么说 这歌听得我舒坦
Well, for some reason it relaxes me.
再来一下Gene Simmons做的那个
Now, do that thing Gene Simmons does.
KISS乐队主唱及贝斯手
死赖四十年就是不闪边儿么?
Overstay my welcome for 40 years?
遗憾是吧? 本地新闻人倒是有一点儿
Regrets, eh? This local newsman's had a few.
此生只报道一窝子小镇乡巴佬
Covering a town of backwater rubes
不知为啥 这帮人还恨我入骨
who, for some reason, hate my guts.
这是Knet Brockman...
This is Kent Brockman...
发自春田大桃游行的现场报道
live at the Springfield Peach Parade.
春田大桃游行 Fuzzy Zoeller大元帅(职业高尔夫球手)
这位先生 能跟我们简要谈谈您的朴实人生智慧吗?
Sir, could you give us eight seconds of your homespun wisdom?
一般人都不知道
It's a little-known fact
桃子会让人脑袋染上虱子
that you can get head lice from peaches.
这是我闺女桃子
Uh, this is my daughter Peaches.
今晚十一点遗憾会来得更猛烈
We'll have more regrets at 11:00 tonight
且等我干掉新开的苏格兰威士忌
following an all-new bottle of scotch.
你那算什么遗憾 "我能看到天气预报女主播"先生
You have regrets, Mr. "I Get to See the Weathergirl From the Side"!
我曾做过有生以来最亏的财务决策
I made the worst financial decision of all time.
该死 不能想它
Oh, I can't think about it.
绝对不能想它 我才不想回忆起来
I won't think about it. I don't want to think about it!
见鬼 想起来了
Oh, I'm thinking about it!
Alley球廊(恶搞美国冰淇淋连锁Alley McCall)
2001年初
天呐... 这是我这辈子见过最酷的保龄球
Oh... that's the coolest bowling ball I've ever seen.
不放过一个击柱
美国投资银行
是贝尔斯登吗?
Hello, Bear Stearns?
我要把我所有的苹果股票都卖掉
I'd like to sell all my Apple stock
拿钱来买个碉堡的保龄球
so I can buy a fancy bowling ball.
我都说了嘛 技术神马都是忽悠
You heard me. Technology is a fad.
厚重黝黑的保龄球才是未来之星
Heavy, black balls are the future.
现在就让我们用烂大街的
Now let us text on our ubiquitous
苹果平板电脑和手机发短信祈福吧
Apple tablets and phones.
都是你害我用不成它
Oh, you cost me a piece of all that!
别哭
Oh, don't cry.
我再来恶心你一下吧
If it makes you feel worse,
我就是买了你抛售股票的人哦
I'm the man who bought the stock you sold.
像你这样的富贵之人应该没有遗憾吧
I'll bet a rich man like you has no regrets at all.
只有一桩
Just one.
我失去过一个女孩
The girl that got away.
她伤了我的第一颗心
She broke my first heart.
那么 在座各位有没有真正无怨无悔的?
So, is there truly anyone among us without regrets?
我无怨无悔
I have no regrets.
是吗 母亲?
Really, Mother?
哎呀 把你给忘了
Oh, I didn't see you there.
我乃贪婪者的教父 穷人的大救星
I'm Father O'Greedy. Dimes for the needy.
Milhouse 你是这场闹剧的下半身吧?
Milhouse, are you the bottom half of that mischief?
天呐
Oh, my.
我的裤子 就像在上的主一般 步调不可捉摸
My pants, like the Lord, work in mysterious ways.
快还我法衣来
Return those vestments.
说到股票投资收益
Speaking of return on investments,
我的苹果股价涨了35倍呢
my Apple stock is up 3,500%.
你肯定是故意让我听到的
Aw, you misheard that on purpose!
旧约时代欧洲基督教会向信徒征取的税
别收什一税 别收什一税
Tithe denied! Tithe denied!
一定得想个办法... 自责一下
Must find way... to blame myself.
想问题时该想什么 全新修订版
书上说我该给你弄个木头靠背
Um, it says I should give you lumbar support.
我最好去躺伐木场
Better go to the lumber yard.
是"靠背" 重点是支撑背部
"Lum-bar." It means "lower back."
你要犯多少次错才吸取教训?
How many times will you make that mistake?
还是给我放放KISS的专辑吧
Just put on the KISS record.
- 哪张? - 只要是《爱之枪》的都行
- Which one? - Anything from Love Gun.
臭书 没想到我还有这一手吧?
Hey, book, are you expecting this?
一不做二不休...
And while I'm at it...
人生首轮12个月 如何让宝宝听进话
婴儿心肺复苏法 如何供孩子上大学
烧吧 又臭又实用的烂书们
Burn, dumb, helpful books.
这火烧的还挺旺的
That is a good fire.
你玩完了 Bart
You're going down, Bart!
- 年少无知啊 - 他不会有事的
- Ah, reckless youth. - He'll be okay.
我是在说他呢
I was referring to him.
曾几何时 我也有那般蓬勃的生气
I had a spring in my step like that once.
那时我还和Lilah在一起
Back when I met Lilah.
千元不换的梦幻巴黎日
Lilah在第七区 (巴黎分区之一) 经营一辆小吃车
Lilah ran a little crepe stand in the seventh arrondissement.
Monty
Monty,
我愿尽我一生躺在这冰冷的阁楼 只为将你尽收眼底
looking at you, I could lie in this unheated garret forever.
这地方有暖气 只不过我还没开
There's heat. I just don't turn it on.
看着你 犹如战火辉映的巴黎中一朵盛开的玫瑰
Seeing you there, in the sweet light of Paris between the wars,
我还有件事要问你
there's a question I must pose.
我为你准备了点东西
I have something for you.
不是这个
Not that.
拿错了
Wrong box.
Lilah 你乐意让我们共进一大步 从兄妹变为伉俪吗?
Lilah, will you take that big step from cousin to wife?
Monty 你要答应我一件事
Oh, Monty, you must promise me one thing.
我为愿她做任何她想要我做的事
Anything she wanted I was willing to do.
任何事 除了...
Anything, except...
我只希望
All I ask is that
你每天花5分钟为别的人着想一下
you set aside five minutes a day to think of others.
那些"别的人"可以换成金条吗?
When you say "others," could they be bars of gold?
我要重新找个老公
I shall find another husband
他的善心一定要大于你的邪恶
as good as you are evil.
世上没有那么善的人
No one's that good.
仅有这些画陪伴着我
All I have left is my drawing.
还是记忆来得更美好啊
It looked a lot better in my memory.
不过你知道吗 Smithers?
Uh, but you know what, Smithers?
我一定要找到Lilah赢回芳心
I will find Lilah and win her back.
先问问我的老友们吧
I'll just check with the old gang.
海明威
Hemingway!
毕加索
Picasso.
西班牙名斗牛士
斗牛士胡安·贝尔蒙特
Matador Juan Belmonte.
还有斯大林
And Stalin.
和他来往够你喝一壶的
That man could really put pressure on you.
你好 Kent
Hello, Kent.
哎呦 哎呦 Rachel Maddow
Well, well, well. Rachel Maddow.
Chip的葬礼把大家都吹回来了
Everyone came back for Chip's funeral.
我正从哥伦比亚特区乘机回纽约呢
I was flying from DC to New York and,
当然 我得在春田镇中途停留一下
of course, I had the layover in Springfield.
第六频道的朋友近来无恙?
How's the gang at Channel 6?
听着 不如我这样和你说吧
Look, let's get this out of the way--
不用和我说我们曾在第六频道共事
just because we both worked at Channel 6
你最后发达了 我却没出人头地的风凉话
and you made it big and I didn't doesn't mean I'm bitter.
这是你的车吗?
Um, Is that your car?
车主苦闷 我恨生活 来挖苦我吧
或许吧
Maybe.
Kent 我是来告诉你
Kent, I'm gonna tell you
你这一生犯的最大的错误...
the most important mistake you ever made...
等我下次候场
after this break.
那么 Kent 你犯的错误
So, Kent, that mistake you made,
那个彻底毁掉你一生的错误
that fundamental, life-changing error,
无以复加的失败 还有...
that cosmic fail, that...
- 快告诉我得了 - 等下次候场吧
- Just tell me already! - After this break.
那时你可以和我一起走
You could have come with me,
但是你却抱着资讯娱乐
but you were suckling the dual teats
和揭明星短的破碗不放
of infotainment and celebrifawning.
Brockman和Maddow放眼春田
那么和我们说说你的新片吧
So, tell us about your new movie.
简直棒极了
It's fantastic.
Rainer Wolfcastle《碎颅者4: 脑震荡》明星
制片方让我们在他们的沙盒里演戏呢
The studio let us play in their sandbox.
- 很好 我们这有一段片段 - 不 不 别放它
- Great. We have a clip. - No! No, don't show it.
那片段的份儿还不足全片最棒的五秒呢
There aren't five good seconds in the whole film.
我不再是新闻记者了 我就是个地理学家
I'm not a newsman anymore, I'm a geologist.
总能发掘出自己潜力的新低
I keep discovering a new rock bottom.
Kent 我想到办法离开这破地方了
Kent, I think I found my ticket out of this town.
或者说 至少也可以在春田镇混好点
Or at least to a better Springfield.
你们俩狗仔想找点新鲜事吗?
You two newshounds working on a story?
听听这个如何?
How about this?
Mario餐馆的意面里发现了死老鼠
Mario's down the street found a rat in their pasta.
什么时候发生的事?
When did that happen?
想啥时候发生就啥时候 你懂的
Whenever you want. Eh?
Rachel 我可以跟你去吗?
Rachel, can I come?
咱俩可以共同报道
We can share blazers.
跟来就是了
Just follow me.
二十世纪巨星 据传与猫王和披头士齐名
Mario家的墙上辛纳屈的签名照
At Mario's, the picture of Sinatra on the wall
辛纳屈的儿子 名气不敌其父
是小弗兰克的亲笔签名
is signed by Frank Junior.
相框把"小"字给挡啦
The frame hides the "Junior"!
有人在森林里乱扔旧轮胎
Someone's been dumping tires in the forest.
软新闻指不敏感不重要的新闻
老天啊 我做了三年的软新闻
Willikers! In my three years of soft news,
从来没见过这种东西
I've never seen anything like this.
这些都是我苦命的小丑车上换下来的
Those are tires from my ill-fated Krusty Town Car.
只要方向盘抓太紧 胎就会爆掉
It would explode if people gripped the wheel too tightly.
真是绝妙的好题材
What a scoop!
不许你们发这条新闻
You're not telling no one.
我做凌晨四点的小丑节目
As the 4:00 p.m. clown,
我对第六频道可有着完全的控制权
I have complete control of the Channel 6 news division.
当地新闻就是个笑话
Local news is a joke.
我要去有线台做节目了
I'm going to cable.
有线台新闻 没劲
Cable news! Bah!
人们只会看看晚间新闻
People only want news at 6:00 p.m.
周一到周五白人播 周末换黑人播那种
from white guys on weekdays and black guys on weekends.
那等着瞧好了 咱们走着瞧
We'll see about that. es, we shall see.
这种事情 绝对有你好看的
About that, things will be seen.
我们会做到
By us.
Kent 怎么不走?
Kent, you coming?
他才舍不得走呢
He ain't comin'.
这头小猪仔才舍不得离开
This little piggy's afraid to leave
他那只安逸的"新闻主播"泔水桶
his cushy anchorman slop trough.
你 呃 能不能说得好听点?
Could you, uh, phrase that a little more nicely?
不好意思 他"不想"走
Sorry. He "isn't" coming.
你会后悔的 Kent
You'll regret this, Kent.
到时候我主持自己的节目 你还在这儿瞎混
When I have my own show and you're stuck here
从北极开始追踪报道圣诞老人行踪什么的
tracking Santa's flight from the North Pole.
"看哪 他现在到达格陵兰上空了"
"Oh, look, he's over Greenland!"
甭担心 猪仔 你的选择没错
Don't worry, piggy, you made the right choice.
烧个把小时就会灭的
Eh, it'll burn out in an hour or so.
过来看 Burns 我搞到你旧爱的线索了
Look, Burns, I've got the dope on your sweetie.
她还活着
She's still alive,
上周才开始不生你的气
and she just got over being mad at you last week.
Lilah她还活着?
Lilah's alive?
是啊 对 活是活着
Yeah, well, uh, she's alive,
但当修女去了
but she's a nun.
跟上帝结了婚是吧 上帝会家暴么?
Married to Jesus, eh? Does he beat her?
绝对不会啊 上帝可是三好学生
Jesus? No, he's a real Eagle Scout, that one.
你的旧欢也不信天主教 她当的是尼姑
But your penguin's not a Catholic, she's a Buddhist nun--
以禅宗花园来消耗性欲 了此残生
spent her life expressing her sexuality with a Zen garden.
那些坚挺的石柱换作是我就好了
Those raked rocks could have been me.
好啦 既然你那么擅长找东找西 自己找门出去吧
Now, since you're so good at finding things, find the exit.
还有个小事情 我的费用问题...
There is the little matter of my fee.
你开始烦人了啊
You're becoming very tiresome.
谁动了我的书桌
Who moved my desk?!
美洲大道
好 我到啦 有线台的地盘
Well, here I am. Cable news alley.
福克斯新闻台
最新发现: 恐龙死于税收过重
微软全国广播公司
由福克斯公司开创
有线电视新闻网
卖新闻 换口饭
福克斯新闻台
你爷爷爱看的新闻台
Fox News.
这就是我真心想要重振旗鼓的大场面吗?
Is this really how I want to get back in the big leagues?
先看看纸媒新闻的气数如何吧
Let's see how print journalism is doing.
先生 你这儿卖《纽约时报》吗?
Sir, do you sell The New York Times?
报刊亭
先生 这就是《纽约时报》总部啦
Sir, we are The New York Times.
我还是进这边吧
And in I go.
你干嘛要这样做 Bart?
Why are you doing this, Bart?
一半是为了博得注意
50% attention-seeking,
另一半是为了空投东西砸人
50% to drop things on people.
他要去看我天上的奶奶了
He's gonna visit my sky granny.
福克斯新闻频道
在福克斯新闻台工作的话
To work at Fox News,
你只要能够操控这个装置就行了
all you have to be able to do is operate this device.
假如共和党人有麻烦的话...
Now, when a Republican is in trouble...
当时 我不知道在国会大厦的台阶上
At the time, I didn't know it was illegal
阿拉巴马州议员 共和党
勾引奶牛是违法的
to sex up a cow on the Capitol steps.
这样做就行啦
... we simply do this.
加州议员 民主党
你来试试
Now you try.
对不起 我刚发现其实我还是有良知的
Sorry, but I just discovered I have some scruples.
我要回我亲爱的小镇去
I'm going back to my sweet little town
在那儿我可以决定播什么新闻
where I can decide what news is.
就像上帝一样
Like a god.
咱俩拥有过美好的回忆
We've had some good times.
♪ Elvis Presley - Memories
♪ 回忆 ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ 在脑海的书页间静息 ♪
♪ Rest between the pages of my mind ♪
♪ 回忆 ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ 如同醇酒将我洞悉 ♪
♪ See me through the ages just like wine... ♪
我脚丫睡觉的时候 就靠你来踩油门了
And you sat on the gas pedal when my foot fell asleep,
所以我一定要把你擦得干净锃亮
so I'm getting you shined up nice.
Alley球廊 苹果零售店 即将开张
搞毛...
What the... ?
这是防"球"玻璃 先生
That's a ball-proof window, sir.
您想要我问一下Siri最近的医院在哪儿吗?
Would you like me to ask Siri for a nearby hospital?
对不起 附近找不到"医猿"
I'm sorry, I don't see any "hops petals" near you.
即将删除所有联系人信息
Deleting all contact information.
不对 我没让你干这个 Siri 我...
No, no, I didn't ask you to do that, Siri. I...
删除已确认
Delete confirmed.
要振作 Bart 要冷静
Oh. Okay, Bart, be cool.
冷静点 你不会死在这上面的
Calm down, you're not gonna die up here.
德州土豪家庭联谊会
山顶小筑
Monty 简直不敢相信这么多年过去了 你会来找我
Oh, Monty, I can't believe you found me after all these years.
我将我所有的爱都留给了你
I've saved myself for you.
这个...
Well, then, uh...
我早该把衣服给脱了
I should disrobe at once.
客房服务吗? 请送一副中式屏风
Housekeeping? Send up a Chinese dressing screen
火石: 美国轮胎品牌
和火石最好的硬化避孕套来
and one of Firestone's finest vulcanized prophylactics.
马上回来
Be right back.
Smithers 我该先用哪一个
Smithers? Which do I take first,
犀牛角 还是老虎舌?
the rhino horn or the tiger tongue?
先生 这两种我都持保留态度
I have my doubts about both, sir.
那我还是用老方法吧
I'll just do it the old-fashioned way.
用泵
With my pump.
我只是补点粉儿 亲爱的
Just powdering my nose, darling.
Smithers 赶紧去西尔斯百货
Smithers, run down to Sears, Roebuck
买一个八分之五英寸的螺钉
and get a five-eighths-inch Phillips head bolt.
我又来了 在每天的5点 6点 11点慢慢的死去
Here I am, slowly dying every day at 5:00, 6:00 and 11:00.
救命 救命
Help! Help!
儿童遇险并具有强烈的视觉冲击
Child in danger with exciting visuals!
这孩子的故事也许能成为我的救命稻草
This kid's corpse could be my magic carpet.
来一个摄影师
Get me a cameraman!
电影《飞屋环游记》的情节在春田镇重演
The movie Up has come horribly to life over Springfield.
当地一个男孩为生命而坚持的这个故事
A local boy clings to life in a story
即时消息: 我惊呼 漂浮吧
证明了播音员的价值
that proves this reporter's relevance.
我的天啊
Ay, caramba!
是Bart
It's Bart!
祈祷奇迹的发生吧 孩子
Pray for a miracle, boy.
在上面上帝能听得更清楚
God can hear you better from up there.
亲爱的上帝 请帮助我安全着陆吧
Dear Lord, please help me land safely.
或者将这个篮子变成一个我能用意念控制的
Or transform this basket into a flying killer robot
飞行机器人杀手 阿门
that I control with my mind. Amen.
这可不是祈祷
That's not a prayer.
我的上帝说是就是
My God says it is.
我感觉到了你冷若冰霜的期盼
I see you're ice-cold with anticipation.
死了?
Dead?
Lilah
Lilah.
即使到了生命的尽头 我还是等待的太久了
Even at the end, I waited too long.
试试给她充满生命力的人工呼吸?
What if I give her the breath of life?
天哪
Oh, boy.
我只能说祸不单行啊
I guess one regret just leads to another.
先生 也许只有一件事能让你得到平静
You know, sir, maybe it would bring you peace
那就是尊重 Lilah 曾经要求过你的事
to honor the one thing Lilah ever asked of you.
食物救济站
这是给你的 先生
Here you are, my good man.
一碗肉汤能温暖你冰冷的心灵
A little broth will cure your mental illness.
先生 已经五分钟了
Sir, that's five minutes.
你可以不用再为其他人着想了
You can stop thinking of other people now.
你知道吗 我想再来五分钟
You know what, I think I'll give it another five.
我为你骄傲 Monty
I'm proud of you, Monty.
我可不会吃这个
I ain't eatin' that.
长官 你要怎么救我们儿子?
Chief, what are you doing to save our son?
我在屋顶上安排了狙击手
Well, I've placed marksmen on the roof
去把气球一个一个的射爆 但是...
to shoot the balloons one by one, but...
老实说 他们技艺可没那么精湛
frankly they're not very good.
长官 又出事了
Chief, it happened again.
赶紧的 伙计们 散开站 一臂间隔
Aw, come on, guys, spread out. Arm's length.
这都是我的错
It's all my fault.
我不该在怀孕的时候听KISS乐队的那些专辑
I should never have listened to those KISS albums when I was pregnant.
Marge 恕我直言 这实在是荒唐
Marge, with all due respect, that's ridiculous.
我家Sarah怀Ralphie的时候
My Sarah listened to Mozart
都是听莫扎特的曲子和丘吉尔的演讲
and Churchill speeches when she was pregnant with Ralphie,
他现在都不敢打开冰箱
and he can't even open a refrigerator.
用推的 都是用推的
Pushing, always... always pushing.
真的?
Really?
是啊 那孩子脑子真乱套
Oh, yeah. That kid's a mess.
嘿 只有我才能批评他 Lou
Hey! Only I get to criticize him, Lou.
那个孩子害怕冲水 觉得那是他的兄弟
Kid's scared to flush. Think's it's his brother.
能不能把注意力放到我那还在天上的儿子身上?
Can we focus on my son up in the sky?
我有一个长远的想法
Oh, I've got a long-shot idea.
我的意思是 在远距离进行发射
By which I mean firing a shot over a long distance.
你看 如果我们能够
Yeah, you see, if we could fire
将12磅半的重量射进那个篮子
an exactly 12-and-a-half-pound weight into the basket,
这将会使孩子慢慢的降落到地面的
it would lower the boy very gently to the ground.
不幸的是 我们所有的炮弹都被熔掉拿去
Unfortunately, all our cannonballs were melted down
美国著名橄榄球教练
制作Joe Paterno的雕像去了
to make a statue of Joe Paterno,
加拿大著名演员
后来我们又将其改造成了Eugene Levy的样子
which we changed to look like Eugene Levy.
我觉得我也许有你们在找的东西
I think I just might have what you're looking for.
今天我很高兴我把那股票给卖了
Today I'm glad that I sold that stock.
苹果今天收盘又涨了20点
Uh, Apple closed up another 20 points today.
为什么每个人都知道?
Why does everyone know?
因为他们可怕的产品会一直为你关注其走势
Because their terrific products keep track of it for you.
还有其他所有你能想到的东西
And anything else you could ever think of.
弧线计算器
绝不能让孩子在我轮班时出事
That kid's not dying on my watch.
幸运的是 轮班 结束了
Which ends... right now, fortunately.
Bart Bart Bart Bart Bart Bart
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
Bart Bart
Bart! Bart!
这可是我们最后一次拍苹果的马屁了
我们还没得到应有的报酬呢
Homer 升的比苹果的股票还快
Homer's rising faster than Apple stock.
我儿子没事儿
My boy's okay!
Bart Bart Bart
Bart! Bart! Bart!
我在科学展览上得了第一名
I won the science fair!
我可以去芝加哥了
I get to go to Chicago!
Bart Bart Bart
Bart! Bart! Bart!
Bart, Bart, Bart.
你知道我是怎么看待遗憾的吗?
You know what I think about regrets?
只要全家人能够在一起
As long as your family is together,
你所做的每一个选择都是正确的
every choice you've ever made is the right one.
我们这不正在一起吗
And together we are.
你们能不能停下来? 他都已经安全着陆了
Would you guys knock it off? He's down safe already.
对不起 长官 放枪走火了
Sorry, Chief, that was me putting it down.
这就是你们所看到的的 家庭重聚
And there you have it-- a family reunited.
一个懂得感恩的国家会感谢真实的报道的
And a grateful nation gives thanks for some solid reporting.
再次交还给你  Rachel Maddow
Back to you, Rachel Maddow.
干得漂亮 Kent
Great job, Kent.
我认为我们在MSNBC中有一个空缺的职位给你
I think we might have an opening for you at MSNBC
节目的时间是在周末的监狱纪实
between our weekend prison documentary block
与周日早上 Joe Scarborough 化妆的两个小时之间
and the two hours it takes to make up Joe Scarborough on Monday morning.
还是算了 谢谢 Rachel Maddow 我在这儿过得挺好的
No, thanks, Rachel Maddow. I'm happy right here.
没有遗憾
No regrets.
纪念Marcia Wallace 享年70岁
Huffington Post: Edna仍会在S25-26中出现 声音已提前录好
@辛普森一家字幕组
weibo.com/spsgroup